看在小羊羔的份上  你在做什么
What in the name of little billy goats are you doing?
我醒得早  再也睡不着了
I woke up early and I couldn't go back to sleep,
所以在读你的小说
so I started reading your novel.
等等  就快看完了
Hold on. I'm almost finished.
可我还没写完呢
Well, I-I on the other hand am nowhere near finished.
有些早期场景故意遗漏了上下文
Um, you know, several early scenes lack context intentionally,
我将在未完成的后续章节中补坑
which will be made clear in the subsequent and as-of-now-unwritten chapters --
嘘
Shh!
我只是想亡羊补牢  降低你的期望
I'm merely just trying to retroactively manage your expectations is all.
我很喜欢
I love it.
我真为你骄傲
And I'm really proud of you.
我上班要迟到了
Oh, I'm gonna be late for work.
知道吗
You know,
我昨天去磨刀时想到了你
uh, I was thinking about you yesterday while I was getting my knives sharpened, and --
我应该担心吗
Should I be alarmed here?
不  我的想法当然没有杀意
Uh, no. The thought which sprang to mind was decidedly not homicidal.
总之  那个刀匠正好也配钥匙
At any rate, this particular cutler also happens to be a key cutter.
我很想多见见你
I want to very much see more of you.
近来你工作很忙
And with your job taking up so much of your time as of late,
我想着这样更方便
I just figured this might make things a little bit easier.
以防我没说清  这是我公寓的钥匙
In case it is not clear, it is a key to my apartment.
史蒂芬妮
Stephanie,
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
顺利吗
So, things went well?
实话说
Well, to put it bluntly,
我五点半要和她一起吃冰淇淋
I'm meeting her for ice cream at 17:30,
我仍然不知道接下来该做什么
and I'm still uncertain as to my follow-up move.
但我能意识到  这是个积极的结果
But I can recognize that what transpired was a positive outcome.
我的参照物很少
I have so little frame of reference,
所以无法想象接下来会发生什么
I cannot hold it conceivable what comes next.
你爱她吗
Do you love her?
那当然
A strong affirmative.
她说她也爱我
And she has said that she reciprocates.
那就放松吧
Then relax.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
当一个女人说爱你时
When a woman tells you that she loves you,
相信她
believe her.
史蒂芬妮  我是尤金
Stephanie. It's Eugene.
你在吗
Are you there?
史蒂芬妮
Stephanie!
史蒂芬妮  我是尤金
Stephanie, it's Eugene.
你在吗
Are you there?
史蒂芬妮
Stephanie!
我是尤金
It's Eugene.
你在家吗  史蒂芬妮
Are you in there, Stephanie?
行尸走肉
第十一季  第十一集
看起来挺好  印吧
Looks good. Put it to bed.
等等
Hold on.
她说看起来不好
She says it doesn't look good.
这句我看懂了
Yeah, I got that one.
戴维斯士兵有故事要说
"Trooper Davis has a story to tell.
他不会冒着被逐出联邦的风险
He wouldn't risk getting kicked out of Commonwealth
无缘无故做这种事
for no reason."
没错  有缘故
That's right. He didn't.
他的医生证实了他有创伤后遗症
We have a statement from his doctors backing up his PTSD claim.
得了吧
"Come on.
军医的话和军方指挥部的话一样不可信
I don't trust the military doctors any more than I trust the military command.
泰勒·戴维斯遭遇了某件事
Something happened to Tyler Davis.
某件他认为错在弥尔顿总管
Something that he blames Governor Milton for.
并值得去公开质疑她的事
Something worth confronting her in public over.
而他们显然因为某种理由在隐瞒真相
And they clearly have a reason for suppressing the truth."
这是一种解释
That's one interpretation.
另一种解释是泰勒·戴维斯有心理疾病
The other is that Tyler Davis had a mental-health crisis.
这两种解释中  只有一种解释有事实支撑
And only one of those interpretations has the facts to support it.
他说过还有上千个像他一样的人
"He spoke of thousands more like him.
这是什么意思
What does that mean?
我们应该...
We should be --"
我们应该印出化装舞会上真正发生了什么
"We should be printing what really happened at the masquerade ball.
但你只想改述弥尔顿总管在通稿中的话
But, instead, you want to paraphrase what Governor Milton said in her press release."
不  康妮
No, Connie.
我要你去改述弥尔顿总管在通稿中的话
I want you to paraphrase Governor Milton's press release
这样下次  我就不用亲自出马了
so that the next time, I don't have to.
既然没人见过她  没人和她说过话
Well, if no one's seen her and no one's talked to her,
那她是怎么请假的
how can she have called in sick?
我从没说她请假了
I never said she did.
我只知道  我来顶班是因为她没现身
All I know is, I was told to be here because she didn't show up.
可以了吗
You mind?
你确定要这样做吗
Are you sure about this?
那个人劫持过人质
The guy took a hostage.
他当时担心自己的安危
He was afraid for his life.
我也担心过自己的安危
I've been afraid for my life,
但我从没有劫持过无辜人质
I've never taken an innocent hostage.
我只是想知道他认为帕梅拉做了什么
I just want to know what he thinks Pamela did.
你之所以想知道
The only reason you want to know
只是因为他们想隐瞒这件事
is because they're trying to keep it a secret.
这是私人病房
This is a private room.
泰勒·戴维斯  他有律师吗
"Tyler Davis -- does he have a lawyer?
他被指控了什么罪名
What are the charges against him?"
联邦军
This is C.A.
我们被要求检查你的安全
We've been asked to perform a wellness check.
请开门
Please open the door.
她不在
She's not there.
那我想立刻作供
Then I'd like to make a statement immediately,
趁我记忆犹新时  详述她最后的行踪
recount the details of her last-knowns on the record now
以供记录在案
while this is still fresh in my mind.
好  来站里一趟  我帮你填文件
Sure. Come down to the station. I'll help you fill out the paperwork.
你常这样出行吗
How often do you take trips like this?
没我希望的那么频繁
Not as often as I'd like.
这听起来可能很疯狂  但是
This probably sounds crazy, but
我感觉比起在城市里  我在外面感觉更好
I feel like I'm better out here than I am in the city.
听起来一点不疯狂
It doesn't sound crazy at all.
我们的很多人也有同感
A lot of my people feel that way, too.
你仍然分你们和我们啊
You still see this as your people and my people.
我想让你看这个地方是如何运作的
I want you to see how this place works,
因为我希望你成为它的一部分
because I want you to be a part of it.
总的来说  我混得还不错
I've done fairly well, all things considered,
但我不是一开始就处在顶端
but let's just say I didn't start out on the top.
你现在算处在顶端吗
Is that where you are now?
勉强算吧
Hardly.
弥尔顿总管管理这座城市
Governor Milton runs the city.
但我知道它是如何运作的
But I know how it runs.
因为你是从底层打拼上来的
Because you started out at the bottom.
很久以前  我向弥尔顿家族证明了我的能力
I proved myself to the Milton family a long time ago.
如果你跟正确的人打交道  卡萝尔
If you're in with the right people, Carol,
你的前途不可限量
the sky's the limit.
向上爬时你会学到
And one of the things you learn as you're climbing your way up
任何组织内都有两种人
is that there are two types of people in any organization.
一种是佣兵
On the one hand, you've got the mercenaries.
他们拿钱干活
They're in it for the money
靠地位来满足自己的某种欲望
and whatever psychological itch their position allows them to scratch.
另一种是爱国者
And on the other, you have the patriots,
忠诚信徒  想做好事的人
the true believers, the ones who want to do good.
至于做的是不是好事也许有待商榷
And whether they are or not might be up to debate,
但他们加入
but in their hearts, they're there
是因为他们真心相信组织
because they believe in the organization.
你让我来就是为了这个吗
Is that why I'm here?
把我改造成忠诚信徒吗
You want to make a true believer out of me?
我读过你的档案
I read your file.
我让你来是因为你够聪明
You're here because you're smart.
我觉得你能帮我应付这个混蛋
I think you'll be able to help me deal with this asshole.
至于你怎么想  那取决于你
What you get out of it is up to you.
我们是什么
What are we?
毒贩还是走私贩
Drug dealers or smugglers?
我们是走私贩
We're smugglers.
但这与你想的不同
But it's not what you think.
这地方严格来说不属于联邦
This place is not exactly a part of the Commonwealth,
但我们需要他们  他们需要我们
but they need us, and we need them.
我们用罂粟为医院制作鸦片
We use the poppies to make opium for the hospital.
如果用完了  那里的情况会变得很糟
Things will start looking pretty bleak there if we run out.
我负责确保这不会发生
I make sure that doesn't happen.
但有时候  我得和莫托这样的人打交道
But, sometimes, that means dealing with guys like Moto.
我说过会发生这种事
I told you what was gonna happen.
而我说过你要处理好
And I asked you to manage it.
我说服他们加工了最后一批货
I talked them into processing this last batch.
我尽力了
Best I could do.
我说过他们会扣下收成的
I told you they're gonna hold the harvest hostage.
他们要求加薪
They want a raise.
如果不加  他们发誓让收成烂在地里
They swear they'll let it rot without one.
我们来看看怎么办吧
Well, let's see what we can do.
我们是《论坛报》的
We're with the Tribune.
去2号
You're in number 2.
太荒唐了
珍知道我对警察军事化怎么看
所以派我来写随队宣传文章
如果你不想惹她生气
也许你应该考虑一下按她的要求办事
就这一次
最近没见到你
I haven't seen you around.
你还好吗
How are you holding up?
在固定范围内我还算正常
I'm functioning within to-be-expected parameters.
嗯  我看出来了
Yeah, no, I can see that.
所以能让我进去吗
Uh, so can you let me in?
我带了千层面
I brought lasagna.
盘子是空的
This is an empty dish.
对  抱歉
Oh, yeah, sorry.
我没做千层面
I didn't make lasagna.
一般带食物别人都会让你进去
People just always have to let you in if you're carrying food.
那么  怎么回事
So, what's up?
联邦军放弃了搜索
When the C.A. Gave up the search,
我决定亲自调查史蒂芬妮的失踪
I decided to investigate Stephanie's disappearance myself.
实话说
Truth be told,
随着时间流逝  线索无迹可寻
as the hours tick by with nary a bread crumb to be found,
我被绝望吞噬了
I let my despair get the best of me.
直到一次偶遇让我发现了端倪
That is, until a chance encounter put me on the trail.
先生
Sir. Sir.
先生  我要和你谈谈
Sir, I need to talk to you.
拜托了  我要谈谈...
Please, I need to talk --
雷辛街1634号
1634 Racine.
一号住宅区的一座公寓楼
It's an apartment building in Residential One.
三天前  你被看到
Three days ago, you were seen --
在晚上七点下了楼梯
at 7:00 in the P.M., you were seen coming down the stairs.
-我不记得了  -等等
- I don't remember this. - Uh, wait.
先生
Uh, sir, sir.
先生  拜托了
Sir, please.
我的一位至亲失踪了
Someone near and dear to me has gone missing,
你也许看到了能帮我找到她的线索
and you may have seen something that might help me find her.
在哪里来着
Where was this?
一号住宅区
Residential One.
三天前  大概晚上七点
Three days ago, at approximately 7:00 in the P.M.
对
Yeah.
一号住宅区
At Residential One.
我现在想起来了
I remember that now.
我被叫去通水槽
I got called in to fix a clogged sink.
你在那里看到她了吗
What -- Do -- Do you remember seeing her there?
Do you remember seeing her there?
或者当晚在附近有没有看到什么可疑情况
Or anything suspicious in or around the premises that night?
没有
No.
够了吗
We done?
我真心抱歉打扰了你
I sincerely apologize for having troubled you.
哪天有空我们可以谈谈...
If there's a better time in which we could talk --
不必说  我对他的说法相当怀疑
Needless to say, I greeted his story with a great deal of skepticism.
当晚街头没有城市服务车
There were no city service carts on the street that night,
他也没有穿着明显制服或携带任何工具
nor was he wearing any sort of identifying uniform or carrying any tools.
在她失踪当晚  唯一一个在场的男人
I found it very peculiar that the one person I knew was there
有如此经不起推敲的托辞  令我非常奇怪
the night she disappeared happened to have such a flimsy alibi.
于是我开始跟踪他
So I started following him.
这个管道工是怎么回事
So, like, what's this plumber's deal?
首先
To start with,
他叫罗曼·卡尔霍恩
his name is Roman Calhoun.
他肯定不是个管道工
And he is most definitely not a plumber.
他通常在晚上办事
He mostly conducts his business at night.
他的行动基地是仓库区的一座大楼
His base of operations is a building in the warehouse district,
这家公司自称是管道服务承包商
which purports to be a purveyor of plumbing services
在表面上看是合法的
and which, on the surface, appears to be legitimate.
不过  他们从没有收到过任何邮件
However, they never receive any mail.
非营业时间里面亮着灯
There's lights on at odd hours, when they're ostensibly closed.
还有人经常进出
And while people go in and out with a fair degree of regularity,
通常都是同样的四个人
it's usually just the same four people over and over.
他们独自抵达  然后很快离开
They usually arrive alone and depart shortly thereafter
经常两人一组会面
and frequently meeting in groups of two.
只有一次全员到齐  并有第五人到场
And on the one occasion they were all together, they were also met by a fifth,
我认为他就是老大
who I also believe to be the head honcho,
他是政府内流氓势力的幕后黑手
the mastermind of some sort of rogue element
史蒂芬妮不知为何得罪了他们
within the government that Stephanie somehow ran afoul of.
流氓势力
Rogue element?
你认为是政府的人绑架了她吗
Like, you think she was kidnapped by the government or something?
在我开始搜索不久之后
Shortly after I began my search,
我后来所知道的二号同谋者
the man who later became known to me as Co-Conspirator Number Two,
也就是"圆帽男"
a.K.A. "Beanie Hat Man,"
来到了史蒂芬妮的公寓
showed up to Stephanie's apartment
带着一队搬家工  带走了她的所有东西
with a team of movers, collected all her belongings,
将之运去了未知地点
and took them to an unknown location.
然后在同一天
Then, that same day,
史蒂芬妮在联合车站的档案中出现了这个
this was found in Stephanie's file at Union Station.
这是史蒂芬妮在失踪当天签的工作调动申请
It's a work-transfer request signed by Stephanie on the day of her disappearance.
那天在无线电室给她顶班的男子
The man who filled in for her at the radio room
说她并没有提前申请过
that day told me she gave no notice whatsoever.
没有权力机构的直接干涉
Such orders could not be falsified or fabricated
这种调令是不可能被篡改或伪造的
without direct influence from within the halls of power.
她知道他们要找她算账
She knew they were coming for her.
在她逃跑以后
When she eluded them,
他们申请了假工作调动来掩盖她的失踪
they filed that false work transfer to cover up her disappearance.
为了取回她搜集的证据  他们运走了她的所有东西
They took all her belongings to recover any evidence she may have gathered,
现在修补漏洞的最后一步只剩抹消她了
and now silencing her is the last step in repairing that leak.
如果我是对的
If I'm right,
她唯一的希望
her only hope
就是我赶在他们找到她之前曝光他们
is for me to expose them before they find her.
今年渔获如何
Good hatches this year?
很好  先生
Yes, sir.
捕了足够的鱼  我现在钓鱼只是为了娱乐
We catch enough that I can actually just do it for fun.
你的爱好也是一项末日技能真好
It's nice when your hobby is also an apocalypse skill.
说得对
Amen to that.
我不能满足他们的要求
So, I can't give them what they want,
但也许我们能各退一步
but maybe we can meet halfway.
他们可以加薪  但必须靠自己挣
They get a raise, but they earn it.
作为奖励
Incentives.
生产更多
Produce more,
挣得更多
make more.
我只能让步到这里了
Best I can do.
看到想看的东西了吗
See what you need to see?
足够了
"More than enough."
现在你该问我他们让你问的问题了
Then this is the part where you ask me the questions they sent you.
泰勒·戴维斯士兵在武装看守下
"It's been a month since former trooper Tyler Davis
住院已经有一个月了
has been in the hospital under armed guard.
他的罪名是什么
What is he being charged with?"
没这个问题吧
That's not one of the questions.
这是否是因为
"Does it have anything to do with the fact
他劫持的人质是你妹妹
that the woman he took hostage was your sister?"
我还在想你什么时候会发现
I was wondering when you were gonna figure that out.
正式的答复是
For the record,
我妹妹他妈的与此无关
the answer is, my sister don't have a goddamn thing to do with it.
他很忠心
"He was loyal,
他被推荐提前晋升
recommended for early promotion --
推荐人是你
by you.
而他后来却觉得军队被政客操控了
And he wound up feeling like the military was being manipulated by the politicians."
如果我是你
"If I was you,
我一定会非常好奇
I would be really interested
我到底在为谁拼命
in who I was risking my life for."
如果我是你
And if I were you,
我也许会好奇我为什么要查一些
I might wonder why I'm out here digging for answers
我们都知道不会被曝光的真相
that we both know will never see the light of day.
混蛋
尤金
Hey, Eugene,
这真的很酷
it's really cool, you know?
你为她做了这么多事
You doing so much for her.
删掉  重写
Strike that. Reverse that.
我只是在偿还我欠她的人情
I'm merely trying to repay what I owe.
一开始  在我们都以为这场灾难
I made a promise to myself in those early days,
几周就会过去时  我向自己许下了一个承诺
back when we thought this would all blow over in a few weeks,
如果我能挺过去
that if I lived through this,
我会追寻梦想  成为一名科幻作家
I'd pursue my dream of becoming a science-fiction author.
我在无线电里  开玩笑地跟史蒂芬妮说过这事
I have jokingly related that story to Stephanie over the radio.
她告诉我
And she told me,
你不能等到挺过去以后
"You can't wait till after you've lived through it,
因为不管你有没有准备好  我们都只拥有当下
'cause ready or not, right now is all we've got."
她给了我勇气去做我一直想做的事
She gave me the courage to do something I've always wanted to do,
如果有人能帮你做到这点
and when someone can do that for you, well...
连"爱"这个词都显得不够用了
...words like love seem insufficient.
该死
Shit.
上吧
Let's go.
你想闯进他的公寓吗
You want to break into his apartment?
对
Yeah.
我不想惹麻烦  尤金
I don't want to get in trouble, Eugene.
我有份小工作  有张小床
I got a little job. I got a little bed.
我可能还会养只小猫
I might get a little cat.
这太不妙了
This is so bad.
他每周二都要跑十英里  雷打不动
His Tuesday 10-mile is ironclad.
他会离开九十分钟
He'll be gone for 90 minutes.
拜托了
Please.
公主
Princess,
他是解答一切的关键  我知道的
he's the key to cracking this whole thing wide open. I just know it.
抱歉不能留下吃炸鱼了
Sorry we can't stay for the fish fry.
下次吧  朋友
Next time, my friend.
好  一言为定
Yeah, deal.
你怎么看
Well, what do you think?
他在剥削他们
He's robbing them.
我和其中一个小队长谈了谈
I talked to one of the lieutenants.
他私吞了你给他们加薪的钱
He's pocketing the money that you give them for raises
并殴打他们  让他们保持沉默
and beating them to keep quiet about it.
他前晚做得太过了
He went too far the other night,
所以他们才会罢工
and that's why they're on strike.
他们会拿回自己的钱
They'll get their money back
我答应的加薪也不会少
and the raise I just promised them.
莫托怎么处理
What about Moto?
我是不会再和他一起钓鱼了
Well, I'm not gonna go fishing with him anymore,
这点是肯定的
that's for sure.
现在就拘留他
Take him into custody now.
搞什么
Hey! What -- What the hell?
别碰我
Get your hands off of me.
霍恩斯比
Hornsby!
你这个娘娘腔
You mother-pussbucket!
尤金
Hey, Eugene?
他跑十英里时下雨了会怎么做
What's this guy do when it rains on his 10-mile run?
鉴于最近缺少降雨
Well, given our recent lack of precipitation,
我还没有这个信息
I've not yet gathered that data.
现在有了  他回来了
Well, you have now. He's here.
我们得离开了
We have to get out of here.
报告他的距离
Count off his range.
什么
What?
他的距离  五十  四十  三十
His range -- 50, 40, 30.
我不擅长这个
I'm not good at that.
告诉我还剩多少时间
Just tell me how much time I have.
哥们  我说了还剩多少时间
Dude, I am telling you how much time you have,
你没时间了
and you have no time.
我看到他们在外面的梯子上
I saw them on the ladder outside.
不可能跑远的
Couldn't have gotten that far.
他们在那里  就是他们
Hey! There they are! That's them!
墨瑟将军  能为你做什么
General Mercer, how can I help you?
33号房的病人
Where is the patient who was in M-33
和看守他的士兵去哪了
and the soldiers that were with him?
33号房没有病人
There's no one in M-33.
我知道
I realize that.
我想问的是  之前在里面的人去哪了
I want to know what happened to the man who was in there.
没有我的批准  他不能被转移
He can't be moved without my authorization.
抱歉  但显然是可以的
I'm sorry, but, apparently, he can.
我真的很抱歉
I'm truly sorry
我逼迫你陪我参加了这场愚蠢的不幸冒险
that I manipulated you into accompanying me on this lame-brained misadventure.
我一定会澄清你没有参与策划计划
I fully intend to make known that you had no role in planning my scheme
也没有参与计划的实施
and no witting part in its execution.
我刚回城里
I just got back in town.
你俩怎么回事
What the hell, you two?
罗曼·卡尔霍恩的身份完全属实
Well, Roman Calhoun is exactly who he says he is.
他是鲁比公司的管道工
He's a plumber at Ruby's.
他们在文书上有点偷懒
They've been a little lazy with the paperwork,
但他们的确与城市有合同
but they do have a contract with the city.
根据这张单据
And, according to this invoice,
在你看到卡尔霍恩先生的当晚
Mr. Calhoun was sent to Stephanie's building
他确实被派去了史蒂芬妮的大楼
on the night you saw him there
修理工作区的水槽
to fix a sink in a work area.
我们在他衣橱里发现的绑架工具包怎么说
But what about the kidnap kit we found in his closet?
那些武器是非法的
Those weapons are illegal.
对你们来说是非法的
For you.
他是正式公民  他有执照的
He's a full citizen. He has a license.
我们很多人都有应急包
A lot of us have go bags,
即使是住在这里很多年的人
even people who have been here for years.
我给卡尔霍恩说了你的事
I told Calhoun your story,
说了史蒂芬妮的事
told him about Stephanie,
解释了你所经历的一切
explained everything you've been through,
精神上受到的折磨
the mental anguish that it's caused you,
他同意不提出指控
and he has agreed to not press charges.
但你不能再骚扰他
But you have to leave him alone.
签个字
Oh, and sign that.
上面写着你情绪失控
It states you were emotionally distraught
在女友失踪后陷入偏执
and in a paranoid state following the disappearance of your girlfriend.
很遗憾这与你想象中的结果不同
I'm sorry this didn't lead where you thought it would.
你看错了卡尔霍恩  你得接受这点
You were wrong about Calhoun, and you need to accept that,
如果你不接受  我就没法帮你了
because if you don't, I'm not gonna be able to help.
我早该知道的
I should have known.
这个阴谋比我最初想象的更黑暗
The conspiracy goes deeper than I initially thought.
哥们  这些不是真的
Dude, none of this is happening!
史蒂芬妮跟你分手了
Stephanie broke up with you.
这太荒谬了
That's utterly absurd.
我之前就这样想了  但我想着
Look, I've been thinking it, but, you know,
你万一看对了卡尔霍恩呢
what if you were right about this Calhoun guy?
但那家伙是个管道工  尤金
But the dude is a plumber, Euge.
你有...  看
You've got -- Mira.
你有史蒂芬妮的工作调令
You've got Stephanie's work-transfer order.
搬家工来搬走了她的家具
Moving guys literally came and took her furniture.
也许事情没那么复杂
Maybe it's not that complicated.
但你给我的第一条建议是
But the first bit of advice you gave me was,
"当一个女人说爱你时  相信她"
"When a woman tells you she loves you, believe her."
对  当一个女人辞了工作
Yeah, well, when a woman quits her job
没告诉你就搬走了时
and moves away without telling you,
也许你也该相信这是真的
maybe you should believe that, too.
我爸爸受够了的那天
The day my dad had enough,
他直接走了
my man just split.
我以为是因为我抽了他的烟
And I thought that it was because I smoked his cigarettes.
我再也没有见过他
And I never saw him again.
所以  谁知道呢
So, who knows?
也许就是这样
Maybe that was it.
你以为你非常了解某人
I mean, you can think you know someone
然后却发现  你压根不了解真正的他
and then find out you never even met them.
对  这很难受
Yeah, it sucks, man.
但这是常事
But it happens all the time.
我理解你为什么会得出这种结论
I can appreciate how you might reach that conclusion.
不过  我知道一个你不知道的信息
However, I'm privy to one piece of data that you are not.
我知道那种感受
I know how it felt.
好吧
Okay.
这只是一种理论
Well, it was just a theory.
特遣部队坚守阵地
第二波尸潮即将到来
我知道你不想听
Look, I know you don't want to hear it,
但你完成了工作
but you did your job.
这是好事  我们不会永远住在这里
That's a good thing. We're not going to be here forever.
不用每天都拼死拼活
Not every day has to be a fight.
暂住在这里本来就该这样
That's what moving here temporarily was supposed to be all about.
也许吧
Maybe.
好吧  姐姐
Okay, sis,
就这样吧
I'll take it.
这是什么
What is it?
一份名单
It's a list of names.
看最后一个名字
Look at the last one.
泰勒·戴维斯
就说我听到动静了
I told you I heard something.
我来处理
I'll handle it.
你耍了我
You played me.
我就知道
I knew.
你为卡尔霍恩的虚假不在场证明提供佐证
You corroborated Calhoun's bogus alibi,
我很确定你参与了掩盖史蒂芬妮的失踪
I was certain you were involved with covering up Stephanie's disappearance.
但我现在才意识到我的妄想有多严重
But now I realize the depths of my self-delusion,
因为在肚子上重重挨了一脚之前
because Occam's razor should have led me to this conclusion
我早该遵照奥卡姆剃刀定律得出最简单的结论
before a well-placed kick to the belly ever did.
从来就没有什么史蒂芬妮
There was never any Stephanie.
她是谁
Who is she?
她是卧底特工吗
Is she an undercover agent?
欠你人情的欺诈师吗
A con artist that owes you a favor?
她演得太真了
Well, she was very convincing.
你利用她打动我的感情  骗我说出了
You used her to pull at my heartstrings and to trick me into telling you
你想知道的关于我们社区的一切
everything you wanted to know about our communities.
你成功了
Well, it worked.
她引我去了火车场
She led me to the train yard,
我们在那里被你抓住了
where we were captured by you!
你认为我好欺负
You thought I wa-- you thought I was an easy mark,
最信任警察
the most trusting of the police, so you --
所以你把我的朋友们一个个拆散
you split off my friends one at a time,
以为我的防线会崩溃  但我没崩溃
thinking I'd break, but I didn't break.
然后她引我去了无线电室  我们再次被抓
Then she led me to the -- the radio room, where we were captured again.
这次你倒是赚翻了
Oh, and you certainly got your money's worth there.
我竟然上了两次当
I actually fell for that one twice!
她说我可以信任你
She's the one that told me I can trust you!
而我信任了
And I did.
她甚至读了我的小说
She even read my book
以获取任何有用的自传式信息
so that she could get any helpful autobiographical information
来满足你的需要
that might serve your needs!
现在你得到了想要的一切  怎么
But now that you've gotten everything you wanted, what?!
骗局没必要再继续了吗
No need to continue the ruse?!
是这样吗
Is that it?!
但你没料到这个反转
But you didn't see this twist.
我一定会让所有人都知道
I am gonna make absolutely certain that everybody knows
你的真面目是什么
exactly who and what you are.
好啊
Okay.
具体来说  是什么呢
And who or what is that, exactly?
恶人
The villain?
鬼怪
The boogeyman?
还是你们遇见的最大贵人呢
Or the best goddamn thing that ever happened to you?
你说得对  尤金
You're right, Eugene.
我是骗了你
I did lie to you.
就像你和你朋友们为了进这里  满口扯谎一样
Just like you and your friends lied through your teeth to get inside these walls.
不
No. No.
但谁会分那么清呢
But who's keeping score, right?
为了让你们来这里  我的确做了一些事
So, I did what I had to do to get you here.
知道吗  你们应该为此感谢我
And you know what? You should be thanking me for it.
你们蠢到不知道天上掉了馅饼可不是我的错
It's not my fault you people are too stupid to know a good thing when it landed in your laps.
你就直接承认了吗
You're just -- you're just admitting it?
我爱上了她  而我所知的她的一切都是假象
I fell in love, and everything I know about her is a fiction!
当你动了真情时  我们试过让你面对现实
Look, we tried to rip the Band-Aid off when we saw it was getting serious,
我用尽办法阻止你寻找她  但你就是不停手
and I did everything I could to get you to stop looking for her, but you wouldn't.
结果闹成了这样
And here we are.
至少你现在能停手了吧
At least you can stop now, right?
当时你们的情况不会好转  尤金
It wasn't gonna get better for your people, Eugene.
他们将会饿死
They were about to starve.
现在你们来了这里
And now you're here
你们的社区得到了修缮
and your community is getting fixed
你们得到了一切  从音乐会到癌症手术
and you've got everything, from concerts to cancer surgery.
而我们对你们的唯一要求
And literally the only thing we've ever asked of you all in return
就是成为对这里有贡献的成员
is to be productive members of society here
只要你们自愿留下
for as long as you choose to stay.
所以  随心所欲地告诉他们吧
So, tell them whatever you want.
你为了出狱签的那份声明
The statement you signed to get out of jail
上面写着你因神经焦虑导致了偏执
says you were suffering from paranoia as a result of nervous strain.
记得吗
Remember?
看看你  尤金
I mean, look at you, Eugene.
这显然对你打击很大
This has obviously taken a toll.
你心碎了我遗憾吗
Am I sorry your heart got broken?
那当然
Absolutely.
我相信你的朋友们听说了一定也很难过
And I'm sure your friends will be very sad to hear about it, too.
但权衡一下
But in the balance of things,
我仍觉得这个结果对大家都好
I still think it worked out in everyone's favor.
他们应该也会这样想
And they probably would, too.
对了
Oh.
顺便说句
By the way,
史蒂芬妮的真名是席拉
Stephanie's real name is Shira.
她讨厌铁娘子乐队
And she hates Iron Maiden.
但她真的很喜欢你的小说
But she genuinely enjoyed your book.
你应该继续写下去
You should stick with it.
尤金
Eugene?
你还好吗
Are you alright?
尤金  我要和你谈谈
Eugene, I need to talk to you.
土豆虫
Tater Bug.
蓝象甲呼叫土豆虫  请回答
This is Blue Weevil to Tater Bug. Please come back.
你是谁
Who are you?
是我
It's me.
我是在无线电里和你通话的人
I'm the one you were talking to on the radio.